[{"answer": "Thanks", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You got it.  Could you maybe not tell anyone about this", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Could you maybe not tell anyone about this", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You got it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You callin' me a thief, my man", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "And if that is your s", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Here, have a Popeye's.  This drumstick ain't for beatin' it's for eatin'", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Could I come with you to getting a Gelati", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "This town is really going to hell lately.  So what part of the city do you live in", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " You have a dog?  What kind", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It's my friend, sir", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What was it called, sir", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " He should have thought of that before he denied me my birthright", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " How about this?  I stay here enjoying my Schnapps and you go back", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, that's terrible, that place..", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You followed him", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I used to get baked like this with my first girlfriend, my friend.  We'd get so stoned she would forget I was a dog", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Actually, she was a sewer rat.  Man, that pissed my parents off", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "She was human", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I dated a Japanese girl once.  My parents disapproved.  Not cause she's Japanese, but cause she was only fifteen", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend?  Two floors up, one window over", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't need luck.  I'm good", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What are you doing", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Why would you be floating", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "My mom wasn't a goat", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "An angel", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Do me", "docId": "littlenicky.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I love you", "qsentId": 28}]